#### **OBJECTIVE**

Motivated and detail-oriented sales professional with eight years of supervisory experience seeking a management position. Seeking an opportunity to apply my advanced knowledge of sales and customer service and my experience with team-building and staff development.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **SENIOR AGENCY MANAGER | SBI Life, (Katni, MP)**

2019 - TILL NOW

Driving business growth and develop a network of contracts to attract new clients, research new market opportunities, making sales projections and forecasting revenues, in line with projected income.

## **COMPUTER ASSISTANT | SAHARA India, Amarpatan (Satna, MP)**

2016 - 2019

Performs basic duties related to information/data processing and the operation of computer and associated peripheral equipment.

### **SALES EXECUTIVE | Money Control (Indore, MP)**

2015-2016

Ensure the availability of stock for sales and demonstrations.

### **EDUCATION**

## MASTER OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION (MBA) | CVR UNIVERSITY

2015-2017

Completed my post-graduation as MBA from CVR UNIVERSITY with 71.57%.

# BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION (BBA) | RDVV UNIVERSITY

2011-2015

Completed my graduation as BBA from RDVV UNIVERSITY, JABALPUR with 60.31%.

### **SKILLS**

- LEADERSHIP SKILL
- BUILDING RELATIONSHIP
- COMMUNICATION SKILL
- TEAM MANAGEMENT
- CUSTOMER SERVICE
- MARKET RESEARCH AND ANALYSIS

### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Got 3 back-to- back promotions in SBI Life insurance within 4 months of confirmation.
- Done ₹ 1.5 Crores of business with my entire team at SBI Life insurance.